<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TrackCovidCluster</string>
    <string name="start">Yes, I want to help!</string>
    <string name="intro_title">Why joining?</string>
    <string name="anonymous">It’s anonymous – all the time!</string>
    <string name="test_positive">Tested positive?</string>
    <string name="not_infected">Not infected.</string>
    <string name="maybe_infected">Possibly infected.</string>
    <string name="infected_text">you reported a positive testing.</string>
    <string name="status">Status</string>
    <string name="status_body">Status shown. You will be notified, if a person reports a positive test, which was close to you within the last days.</string>
    <string name="change_status">Change status</string>
    <string name="change_status_body">If your test result is positive, all people will be notified anonymously which were close to you within the last 14 days.</string>
    <string name="future_status_subtitle_1">Your status will be changed to</string>
    <string name="future_status_subtitle_2">change</string>
    <string name="save_lives">Yes, I want to save lives!</string>
    <string name="change_status_reminder">It is not necessary to change back status. After calculated time your status will be reset automatically. However, you can change if it happened by måistake.</string>
    <string name="report">Somebody had a positive result! Please, contact your doctor or 116117 (Germany) for any further question.</string>
    <string name="report_2">If you are positive, please, change your status that others having been in touch with you can be tested.</string>
    <string name="notification_title">You might be infected</string>
    <string name="notification_body">You were in touch with a recently infected person!</string>
    <string name="intro_text2">Get an early warning if you were in touch with an infected person.
        With this you will have the chance to save your beloved ones from infection. Or helping others if you get infected yourself.</string>
    <string name="change_status_to_infected">Your contacts within the last 14 days will be notified ANONYMOUSLY.</string>
    <string name="introText2">Tracking works with low energy bluetooth. So that it works on your mobile phone, access to your location is required. However, it will NOT be prompted or recorded.</string>
    <string name="introTitle2">Why does the app require the location although it won’t be recorded?</string>
    <string name="i_tested_positive">Yes, I got a positive result on a COVID-19 testing!</string>
    <string name="warning">Do not mark yourself as infected without a positive test</string>
    <string name="notification_setting_title">"TrackCovidCluster - Notify me if I am at risk"</string>
    <string name="notification_setting_description">"Infection risk"</string>
</resources>
